manhuntdaily.com 2009-07-04

# Privacy Policy

Online Buddies, Inc., (“OLB”) operators of the Manhunt.net Web site (“Site”), is committed to respecting your privacy. We take reasonable precautions to protect personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We also take reasonable steps to ensure that personal information is relevant for the purposes for which it is to be used. Because the Site is global, information about you that we collect or that you submit may be transferred to, processed in, and held in countries other than the one in which you reside. By using the Site you explicitly consent to such use of your information. 

Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This policy will let you know the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from me?
  2. What are cookies and tracking pixels and how they are used by OLB?
  3. How is my information used?
  4. Who is collecting my information?
  5. With whom will my information be shared?
  6. How can I access, update or delete my information?
  7. What does “opt-out” mean?
  8. What else should I know about my privacy?
  9. Other legal notices.

## 1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from me?

On some Manhunt Web pages, you can make payments and requests and/or receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are your name, gender, age, e-mail address and standard contact information, including addresses and phone numbers and your screen name. 

We may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with the services we provide and contact preferences. Wherever OLB collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

## 2\. What are cookies and how they are used by OLB?

We automatically collect certain information to help us understand how you use the Site. Each time you visit Manhunt.net, we automatically collect your IP address (the Internet address of a computer), browser and computer type, access times, the web page from which you came and the web page(s) you access. In addition, OLB may place Internet cookies on your hard drive or use tracking pixels embedded in our web pages. Internet cookies are small files that may be placed on your hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies and tracking pixels are used to (a) remind us of who you are in order to deliver you better service; (b) estimate our audience size by determining repeat usage of the Site to help target advertisements based on user interests and behavior; (c) track your progress and entries in promotions, sweepstakes and contests, if any; and (d) measure certain traffic patterns for use as a research tool to understand how our users’ habits are similar or different from one another. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. By not accepting cookies, some Web pages may not display properly or you may not be permitted to access certain information.

OLB may also collect IP addresses to track a user’s session while the user remains anonymous. We analyze this data for certain trends in statistics, such as which parts of our Site users are visiting and how much time they spend there.

## 3\. How is my information used?

OLB will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others without your consent. The information you provide will be used to support your customer relationship with OLB. Your information may be shared with agents, contractors or business partners for the purpose of performing services for OLB. 

We want to help you quickly find information on Manhunt and be alerted to specific offers, updated information, and other new products and services from Manhunt. Accordingly, we may send you an e-mail to your external e-mail address about a special contest or promotion or about our various products and services or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply “opt-out” by the means provided for in the mailings or by contacting [support@manhunt.net](mailto:support@manhunt.net). 

Notwithstanding, OLB does research on our users’ demographics, interests and behavior based on the information provided to us during your use of the Site. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information. OLB may share this aggregated data with others. 

## 4\. Who is collecting my information?

When you are on the Site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with OLB alone, unless specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than OLB or an agent for OLB, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service or purchasing those particular goods.

Please be aware that Manhunt advertisers or Web sites that have links on our Site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Web sites linked to Manhunt either through advertisements or other hyperlinks are not covered by this privacy statement.

## 5\. With whom does OLB share my information?

We may share the personal data you provide with other OLB agents, contractors or our business partners for the purposes of performing services for OLB. OLB also may share aggregated data with others. Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information. Notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, we also believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Terms of Access or Use, or as otherwise required by law. Such circumstances where we will share information include: (1.) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or demands; (2.) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person; (3) if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding situations that involve abuses of our network infrastructure or the Internet in general (such as voluminous spamming, denial or service attacks or attempts to compromise the security of the Site or our network infrastructure). Except as provided above or in the event of a merger, consolidation, or sale of all or substantially all of OLB’s assets, we will not share any of your information with any third party without your permission. 

## 6\. How do I access, update or delete my information?

You can request the individual information that OLB has collected about you, correct factual inaccuracies in your information, remove personal information from OLB’s databases and/or update your personal information here or by contacting [support@manhunt.net](mailto:support@manhunt.net). Please note however, that we reserve the right to send you administrative messages relating to the Site, including messages about changes to this Privacy Policy. If at any time you would like us to deactivate your member profile and remove it from public and member viewing on the Site, please e-mail us at [support@manhunt.net](mailto:support@manhunt.net). Please note that we will retain your personal information in back-up storage after deactivation and we are not responsible for removing information about you from the database of any third parties to whom you previously authorized us to share your personal information. 

## 7\. What does “opt-out” mean?

To “opt-out” means that you have notified OLB that we no longer have permission to use your information for an enumerated particular purpose. For example, when we send you information on a new product to your external e-mail account, you will be given the opportunity to “opt-out” of receiving such information in the future.

## 8\. What else should I know about my privacy?

Third party Internet sites and services accessible through the Site have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. OLB has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. Please be careful and responsible online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your information, OLB cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information through the transmission process and you do so at your own risk.

## 9\. Other Legal Notices.

Any dispute over privacy is subject to this privacy policy and our Terms of Access and Use, including limitations on damages and application of the law of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. If you have any concern about your privacy in connection with this policy, please send us a thorough description to [support@manhunt.net](mailto:support@manhunt.net), and we will try to resolve it. We may post a revised Privacy Policy on our Site. Please note that the use of information that we gather is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. You should check our Site frequently to see recent changes.
